export default data = [
  {
      question: "John is very close to his family. Whenever he feels depressed, he returns to the warm, ______, and comfortable atmosphere of his home.",
      options: ["crucial","sloppy","secure","cautious"],
      correct_option: "secure"
  },
  {
      question: "Tom ______ something before he left the room, but I couldnâ€™t figure out exactly what he said.",
      options: ["mumbled","perceived","summoned","trampled"],
      correct_option: "mumbled"
  },
  {
      question: "The content of the book is very much technical and specialized; it is too difficult for a ______ to understand.",
      options: ["patriot","hacker","layman","tenant"],
      correct_option: "layman"
  },
  {
      question: "Food shortages are one of the main causes of ______ nutrition among children in developing countries.",
      options: ["distinctive","vigorous","inadequate","abundant"],
      correct_option: "inadequate"
  },
  {
      question: "Good writers do not always write ______; on the contrary, they often express what they really mean in an indirect way.",
      options: ["explicitly","ironically","persistently","selectively"],
      correct_option: "explicitly"
  },
  {
      question: "According to the weather report, some light rain or ______ is expected today. You may need to take an umbrella with you when you go out.",
      options: ["hail","breeze","tornado","drizzle"],
      correct_option: "drizzle"
  },
  {
      question: "The movie was so popular that many people came to the ______ conclusion that it must be good; however, many professional critics thought otherwise. ",
      options: ["acute","naive","confidential","skeptical"],
      correct_option: "naive"
  },
  {
      question: "In ancient times, people used large shells to ______ voices in open-air ceremonies so that their tribal members near and far could hear what was said.",
      options: ["amplify","mobilize","penetrate","undermine"],
      correct_option: "amplify"
  },
  {
      question: "The audience held their breath and sat motionless in the theater as they watched the tragic historical event ______ in front of their eyes.",
      options: ["ascending","elaborating","illustrating","unfolding"],
      correct_option: "unfolding"
  },
  {
      question: "According to government regulations, if employees are unable to work because of a serious illness, they are ______ to take an extended sick leave.",
      options: ["adapted","entitled","oriented","intimidated"],
      correct_option: "entitled"
  },
]